<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StemiApp</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

    <!-- Login Strings -->
    <string name="registration"><u>Not Registered?</u></string>
    <string name="forgot_password"><u>Forgot Password?</u></string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- SignUp Strings -->
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirmPassword">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="alreadyResitered"><u>Already Registered?</u></string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- Forgot Password Strings -->
    <string name="regEmail">Enter registered email id </string>
    <string name="forgot_password_subheading">We’ll send a new password to this email id, using that you can then set a new password.</string>
    <string name="reset_password">We’ve sent a new password to your email id, enter it below and set a new password.</string>

    <!-- Intro screen Strings -->
    <string name="chest_pain">Recognise Chest Pain Symptoms</string>
    <string name="nearest_hospital">Find Nearest Heart-Attack Ready (STEMI) Hospital</string>
    <string name="stay_healthy">Stay Healthy</string>
    <string name="track_medication">Track Your Medication</string>

    <!-- Health Related Question-->
    <string name="Do_you_smoke">Do you smoke?</string>
    <string name="had_heart_attack">Did you had a heart attack before?</string>
    <string name="have_diabetes">Do you have diabetes?</string>
    <string name="have_blood_presssure">Do you have high blood pressure?</string>
    <string name="have_cholesterol">Do you have high cholesterol?</string>
    <string name="had_paralytic_stroke">Did you ever had a paralytic stroke?</string>
    <string name="have_astama">Do you have bronchial asthma?</string>
    <string name="family_health">Did anyone in your immediate family had a heart attack?</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="gps_network_not_enabled">Location services is turned off, please enable</string>
    <string name="open_location_settings">ENABLE</string>
    <string name="cancel">CANCEL</string>

    <!-- Heart Attack Symptoms-->
    <string name="heart_pain">Pain / discomfort in Chest</string>
    <string name="jaw_pain">Pain in Jaw / Neck / Arm / Shoulder / Back</string>
    <string name="shortnessOfBreath">Shortness of breath</string>
    <string name="lightheadednes">Lightheadednes</string>
    <string name="vomitting">Nausea or Vomitting</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_registration">NewRegistrationActivity</string>


    <string name="learn_more"><u>Learn More</u></string>
    <string name="sync_stemi">Sync with nearest heart-attack ready (STEMI) Hospital</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reset_password">ResetPasswordActivity</string>


    <!-- Privacy Strings-->
    <string name="privacy">This Privacy Policy applies to the CardiaCare Application (hereinafter referred to as the "App" or “CardiaCare”) owned by the STEMI India Charitable Trust (“STEMI India”), a not-for-profit organisation having its registered office situated at #204-205, Poongothai Nagar, Civil Aerodrome, Coimbatore – 641014.
        STEMI India recognizes the importance of maintaining your privacy. We value your privacy and appreciate your trust in us. This Policy describes how we treat user information we collect on CardiaCare. This Privacy Policy applies to all users of CardiaCare. By using and/or entering data into our App, you agree to this Privacy Policy.</string>

    <string name="collect_info">What information do we collect?</string>
    <string name="collect_info_answer">Contact information:\nWe may collect details such as your Name, Email ID, Phone Number and Address.\nPayment and billing information:\nWe do not collect your billing name, billing address and payment method. We NEVER collect your credit card number or credit card expiry date or other details pertaining to your credit card on our App.\n
        Demographic information:\nWe may collect demographic information about you, or any other information provided by your during the use of our App. We might collect this as part of a survey as well.\n
        Medical information:\nWe may collect information regarding your health profile such as whether you have diabetes, dyslipidemia or heart disease.\n
        Information about your lifestyle:\nWe may collect information about your lifestyle such as when and how much you exercise, how stressed you feel and when you smoke.\n
        Other information:\nWe may collect information about your IP address and the browser you\'re using. We might look at what site you came from, duration of time spent on our website, pages accessed or what site you visit when you leave us. We might also collect the type of mobile device you are using, or the version of the operating system your computer or device is running.</string>

    <string name="how_to_collect_info">How do we collect information?</string>
    <string name="how_to_collect_info_ans">Direct collection:\nWe collect information directly from you when you enter details on your App or when you grant permission to upload your details to a STEMI Hospital. We also collect information if you post a comment on our websites or ask us a question through phone or email.</string>

    <string name="personal_info">How do we use your personal information?</string>
    <string name="personal_info_ans">To contact you:\n •	We share information you agree explicitly to share with the STEMI Hospitals in case of an emergency and you would like to reduce time to diagnose and treat a heart attack.\n •	We might use the information you provide to contact you for follow up on treatment you received.\n •	We might use your information to remind you of follow-up medication or check-ups.\n
        To improve our services:\n •	We use information to improve our services. We might use your information to customize your experience with us. This could include displaying content based upon your preferences.\n •	We use information to look at site trends and customer interests. We may use your information to make our App and services better.\n •	We may combine information we get from you with information about you we get from third parties.\n
        To ensure security:\nWe use information for security purposes. We may use information to protect our company, our customers, or our websites.
        To abide by laws:\nWe use information as otherwise permitted by law.</string>

    <string name="third_party_info">Do we share information with third-parties?</string>
    <string name="third_party_ans">•	We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.\n •	We share information with vendors who help us manage our online registration process or transactional message processors. Some vendors may be located outside of India.\n
          •	We may share information to comply with the law or to protect ourselves\n •	We will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may also share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. Or, we might also share information when we are investigating potential fraud.\n</string>

    <string name="third_party_sites">What about third-party sites?</string>
    <string name="third_party_sites_ans">If you click on one of the links to third-party websites, you may be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of those websites. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third-party sites.</string>

    <string name="grievance_officer">Who is the grievance officer?</string>
    <string name="grievance_ans">In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:\n
        Grievance Officer Name: Mr. Jerry David\n
        Address: First Floor, AGT Business Park, 25,Electronics Estate, Avinashi Road, Coimbatore - 641014.\n
        Phone: +91 422 4394546\n
        If you have any questions about this Policy or other privacy concerns, you can also email us at stemicardiacare@gmail.com.</string>

    <string name="jurisdiction">What about jurisdiction?</string>
    <string name="jurisdiction_ans">If you choose to install the App, your installation and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and the App\'s Terms and Conditions. In addition to the foregoing, any disputes arising under this Policy shall be governed by the laws of India. Any legal action or proceeding relating to or arising from your access to or use of this Site shall be instituted in Coimbatore, India. You agree to submit to the jurisdiction of courts of Coimbatore, India and agree that the venue in these courts is proper in any such legal action or proceeding.</string>

    <!-- Terms and Condition Strings-->
    <string name="terms_condition">This document is an electronic record under the Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules thereunder as applicable and the amended provisions of the same. This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.\n\nThis document is published in accordance with the provisions of Rule 3 (1) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries guidelines) Rules, 2011 that require publishing the rules and regulations, privacy policy and Terms of Use for access or usage of the CardiaCare Application.\n\n
        The CardiaCare Application (hereinafter referred to as the "App" or “CardiaCare”) is owned by the STEMI India Charitable Trust (“STEMI India”), a not-for-profit organisation having its registered office situated at #204-205, Poongothai Nagar, Civil Aerodrome, Coimbatore – 641014.</string>

    <string name="acceptance">Welcome to CardiaCare. Before using our services, please familiarise yourself with our terms and conditions. If you do not agree with these terms, please discontinue usage of our application.\n\nYour use of the App and services and tools are governed by the following terms and conditions ("Terms and Conditions") as applicable to the App including the applicable policies which are incorporated herein by way of reference.
        For the purpose of these Terms and Conditions, wherever the context so requires "You" or "User" shall mean any natural or legal person who has agreed to become a user on the App by providing Registration Data while registering on the App as Registered User. The term "We", "Us", "Our" shall mean STEMI India.\n\nBy using our App, you agree to being a person competent to enter into a contract as governed by The Indian Contract Act of 1872. You agree that you are bound by the Terms and Conditions and any other additional rules, guidelines and restrictions that may be posted in specific sections of this App. All such additional rules, guidelines and restrictions are hereby incorporated by reference into these Terms and Conditions. STEMI India reserves the rights to changes these terms and conditions as it deems fit, at any time, without prior notice. You need to review these Terms and Conditions each time before you use this App.</string>

    <string name="copyright">This App contains graphics, photographs, images, artwork, text, fonts, software tools, and other information (referred to herein as “Content”). This App and all Content are copyrighted property owned by STEMI India or the copyrighted property of parties from whom STEMI India has licensed such property. All rights for this App and its Content are reserved worldwide. It is strictly prohibited to retain, copy, distribute, publish, or use any portion of the Content except as expressly allowed in these Terms and Conditions. STEMI India reserves the right to add to, delete from, or modify any part of the Content at any time without prior notice.</string>

    <string name="user_info">CardiaCare provides the facility to its users to enter and maintain records of personal health, and in case of an emergency such as a heart attack, to upload these records with permission to a hospital capable of diagnosing and treating ST-Elevation Myocardial Infarction (STEMI) that is part of the STEMI network and implements the STEMI India Model (“STEMI Hospital”).\n\nCardiaCare also provides the facility to upload photographs. You agree that you will not upload to CardiaCare any photographs which contain material that is unlawful, threatening, abusive, libellous, defamatory, obscene, vulgar, pornographic, profane or indecent, including without limitation any transmissions that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any local, state, national or international law; or\n\n
        •	upload to CardiaCare any content or any other information which contain material which violates or infringes upon the rights of others, including privacy, moral or publicity rights, copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights without first obtaining permission from the owner or right holder; or\n
        •	upload to CardiaCare any photographs or any other information which contain material that contains viruses, worms, corrupted files, or any other form of corruptive code.\n\n
        You understand that the material uploaded on CardiaCare in any form is the responsibility of the person who uploaded it. STMEI India has no obligation to monitor the content submitted. However, STEMI India reserves the right to decide whether any material or content uploaded is prohibited or not and to remove any content or material that in STEMI India’s sole discretion are objectionable or in violation of this terms and conditions stated in this Agreement.</string>
    
    <string name="consent">This informed consent is for users entering data into CardiaCare.\nSTEMI India has been set up with the aim of bringing about universal access to heart-attack care in India. ST-Elevation Myocardial Infarction (STEMI) is the deadliest form of heart attack, the number one cause of death in India. It affects 3 million patients in India every year, of which only a very small fraction get access to any treatment at all.\n
        The STEMI India Model is the framework that has been recommended by the Indian Council of Medical Research as the National STEMI Protocol. It is a hub-and-spoke model that combines remote diagnosis with appropriate treatment protocols and also ensures BPL-insurance scheme benefits so that the poorest of the poor get access to top-of-the-line treatment.\nHospitals that implement this Model are in the STEMI Network. While using CardiaCare to upload your details into the STEMI Hospital device, you agree to share the details entered into the App with the STEMI Hospital. This will help save time in entering details during an emergency and will enable faster diagnosis – a crucial part of successful treatment of STEMI.\nYour agreeing to share information is entirely voluntary.\nBy agreeing to these terms, you permit STEMI India, the doctor at the STEMI Hospital and his collecting staff to access the medical records and use it for diagnosis and deciding on appropriate treatment strategies. Academic research may be conducted using the data collected in order to better improve care for patients with heart attack and thus save lives. Research results may be published in medical literature, but the user will not be identified and all personal details such as names, phone numbers and email addresses will not be shared and will be completely secure.\n</string>

    <string name="use_of_app">You are granted permission to access and use this App and its Content for the sole purpose of maintaining and tracking your health records, learning about heart attack and how to lead a healthy lifestyle to reduce risks, and to contact your closest heart-attack-ready STEMI Hospital in case of an emergency. STEMI India is in no way responsible for the response or arrival of the ambulance, responsiveness of the STEMI Hospital or treatment of the patient. Management of heart attack upon transfer to appropriate hospital will be as per the hospital’s policies and protocols. You agree to use this App in a responsible manner that is in full compliance with these Terms and Conditions and with your local laws and regulations. Without limitation, no portion of Content may be utilized for any unlawful purpose or use, to defame any person, to violate any person’s right of privacy or publicity, to infringe upon any copyright, trade name, trademark, service mark or other intellectual property right of any person or entity. You agree that you are responsible for protecting your password and controlling access to your registered account.</string>
    
    <string name="indemnification">You agree that you shall indemnify and defend STEMI India and all parties from whom STEMI India has licensed portions of Content, and their directors, officers, and employees, against all claims, liability, damages, costs and expenses, including reasonable legal fees and expenses arising out of or related to (i) your breach of these Terms of Use or (ii) any suit, claim, or demand arising from or relating to any text, content, information, photograph, image, graphic or other material you incorporated into Products that was not part of the standard App Content.</string>
    
    <string name="disclaime_of_warrenty">The content and material from or through the App are provided "as-is," "as available," with "all faults", and all warranties, express or implied, are disclaimed (including but not limited to the disclaimer of any implied warranties of merchantability, non-infringement, freedom from error, and fitness for a particular purpose). The information and services may contain bugs, errors, problems or other limitations. The App has no liability whatsoever for your use of any information or service. in particular, but not as a limitation thereof, the App is not liable for any indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages (including damages for loss of life, business, loss of profits, litigation, or the like), whether based on breach of contract, breach of warranty, negligence, product liability or otherwise, even if advised of the possibility of such damages. The negation and limitation of damages set forth above are fundamental elements of the basis of the agreement between the app and you. This app and the products, services, documents, content and materials and information presented would not be provided without such limitations. No advice or information, whether oral or written, obtained by you from us through the App or otherwise shall create any warranty, representation or guarantee not expressly stated in this agreement. All responsibility or liability for any damages caused by viruses contained within the electronic file containing a form or document is disclaimed.</string>

    <string name="limited_warrenty">CardiaCare concedes to provide efficient, reliable, timely and satisfactory service to the best of its resources and skills. STEMI India makes no warranty that the App will be uninterrupted, error free, and virus free or free from any malicious content. The App is provided on an "as is where is" and "as available" basis.</string>

    <string name="liabalities">STEMI India shall not be liable for any loss, injury, claim, liability, or damage of any kind resulting in any way from (a) any errors in or omissions from the App or any services or obtainable therefrom; (b) the unavailability or interruption of the App or any features thereof; (c) your use of the App; (d) the Content and Materials contained on the App; or (e) any delay or failure in performance beyond the control the App.</string>

    <string name="feedback">Any comments, suggestions, proposals or other feedback (collectively “Feedback Information”) provided to STEMI India in connection with the operation or content of this App shall be provided by the submitter and received by STEMI India on a non-confidential basis. All such comments, suggestions, and other information shall become the exclusive property of STEMI India. By submitting any such information to STEMI India, you agree that you are transferring and assigning, at no charge, all of your right, title and interest in the information, including all copyrights and other intellectual property rights. You agree that STEMI India shall be free to use such information on an unrestricted basis.</string>

    <string name="governing_law">Please read these Terms and Conditions carefully. These Terms and Conditions govern your access and use of this App which is hosted by STEMI India. All issues related to the protection, infringement, or misuse of copyrighted materials shall be governed by the copyright laws of India. All other matters relating to your access to or use of this App shall be governed by the laws of India. Any legal action or proceeding relating to or arising from your access to or use of this App shall be instituted in Coimbatore, India. You agree to submit to the jurisdiction of courts of Coimbatore, India and agree that the venue in these courts is proper in any such legal action or proceeding. You also agree that you will not assert in any legal action or proceeding involving STEMI India that a court sitting in Coimbatore, India is an inconvenient forum for such legal action or proceeding.</string>



</resources>
